Why did you come alone?
Where is Yaya?
She's busy with work.
I bought you some food. It's in the kitchen. Remember to eat it.
Take it away. I don't want it.
Bring Yaya back to me.
She won't come back.
She's living a good life now.
You don't need to worry about her.
Damn girl.
She would have a good life living with me too.
You're exactly like your dead mother.
Hurry up and bring Yaya back to me.
I only have one daughter left now.
She needs to live with me.
Why do you think we left you?
To pay off your gambling debts.
We're already living a hard life.
When have you ever fulfilled your responsibilities as a father?
Leave.
It doesn't matter how you torture me.
I won't give Xiaoya back to you.
I've already transferred this month's money to you.
Damn girl. Get out.
Get out. Get out of here.
Pay me back the money.
Open the door.
Hurry up.
Sis.
What should we do?
Hurry up and open the door.
I know you're inside.
Don't be afraid.
Open the door now.
Hurry up.
Money.
Hurry up and open it.
I will figure something out.
Pay back the money. Hurry up.
Lawyer Gu.
Actually, I told Lingze about your father
because I wanted to help you.
It's okay.
So far, it seems your decision was right.
You think so too?
Actually,
I think we both misunderstood Lingze.
It's getting late.
Go back and get some rest.
You have to work tomorrow.
Bye.
Don't move.
It's out of battery.
Why are you staring at me?
These materials are some financial statistics.
Will they be strong evidence?
They are useful.
But these can only serve as indirect evidence.
Although they can make the authorities thoroughly investigate Ling Hengsheng,
the Ling Group is deeply rooted,
and Ling Hengsheng is ruthless.
With just these,
he will definitely find a loophole to escape.
So what do you think?
I still need more evidence.
To be honest,
I really don't believe that my father
exchanged his life for only this much evidence.
Then do you think Ling Ze
intentionally hid important evidence?
What would be his purpose for doing that?
Since he already wants to use our hands
to bring down his father,
there is no need for him to hide anything from us.
For now,
Ling Ze should be fine.
Although I still can't trust Ling Ze,
I will support your every decision.
Just go for it.
No matter what happens,
I will always be your backup.
Thank you.
I am reporting with my real name
that the Ling Group
is suspected of illegal economic crimes,
and forces its artists
to engage in illegal fundraising
and prostitution.
Wait.
Please don't go.
Stay with me.
Thank you
for saving me time and time again.
You are like
a guardian angel.
No one else saved you
but yourself.
I am no god.
I can't help that many people.
My power is limited.
I can only use it to protect you.
In my past life,
I was the one who harmed you.
In this life,
no matter the cost,
I will make it up to you.
Are you numb?
I said, are you numb?
What?
My arm is numb. Could you move a bit?
Women really do have two faces.
Where are we going this time?
To find Hao Zhenshi.
This early?
Yeah.
I think finding him early
means we can protect him in advance.
We can also ask him about the recent changes in Lingze
and see what he thinks.
You've gotten smarter.
I've always been smart, okay?
You
look a bit unusual today.
What's different?
Do you
have a fever?
I'm leaving.
By the way.
Sorry.
What's
wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just want to remind you
that once we go in,
you'd better keep your distance from him
in case he has a sudden episode and hurts you.
Got it.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Hurry!